Dear KEAM 2025 candidate,

Greetings from College of Engineering Kidangoor. The webinar KEAM 2025 Last minute Boost : Top tips for Success in Engineering Entrance will start exactly at 7:00 PM today 21-04-2025.

Please join on time using the following Google meet link.

To join the video meeting, click this link: https://meet.google.com/xzh-vcnk-ggs
Otherwise, to join by phone, dial +1 267-483-1643 and enter this PIN: 771 627 415#
To view more phone numbers, click this link: https://tel.meet/xzh-vcnk-ggs?hs=5